<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://blog.owlfox.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.owlfox.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lalala.. Laravel!</title>
      <link>https://blog.owlfox.org/posts/laravel_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.owlfox.org/posts/laravel_notes/</guid>
      <description> I am reviewing concepts of laravel before doing a part-time job.
routes What is it?
Defines how laravel do with the routes on our webpage. For example: https://myawesomesite.org/test, we can define what laravel should return to this request. Things to be returned can be a html or json for AJAX request.
Where it is?:
 Before laravel 5.3: app/Http/routes.php After: routes/web.php  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First post!</title>
      <link>https://blog.owlfox.org/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.owlfox.org/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post with hugo. Thanks to hugo, hyde-hyde and github pages.
changelog  2018/08/16 Add some hugo command notes  hugo commands hugo new posts/hugo_notes.md  This command will generate a new article based on archetypes/default.md
hugo server  start a local http server, helpful to preview the results before push.
hugo  generate a static site contents into public folder based your current configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first debian conf :)</title>
      <link>https://blog.owlfox.org/posts/debian-conf-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.owlfox.org/posts/debian-conf-2018/</guid>
      <description>I was so lucky to be able to attend this summer and helping the video team to accomplish some tasks!
What is debian conf? DebConf is the Debian Project&amp;rsquo;s developer conference. Where Debian developers(DDs) came from everywhere.
I wish I could contribute more and be more involved into the debian community next year in Brazil.
What I have done? Basically I am doing some simple tasks like handing the camera(The camera operator), the guy who plays with the PA system(audio techinician), director(controlls which camera to feed into the live-stream) during the debconf.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>